Guide to the Records of The Bolivia Project RISM RG 8
New York University Archives
- Appendix: Audiovisual Materials
  - Compi School, Bolivia A & B (Umatic dub and Umatic master), 1969 (Box 314, Item 3)
  - Bolivia C & D (Umatic dub and Umatic master), 1969 (Box 314, Item 4)
  - Bolivia E & F (Umatic dub and Umatic master), 1969 (Box 314, Item 4)
  - Bolivia G & H (Umatic dub and Umatic master), 1969 (Box 314, Item 6)
  - Bolivia J & K (Umatic dub and Umatic master), 1969 (Box 314, Item 7)
  - Bolivia L & M (Umatic dub and Umatic master), 1969 (Box 314, Item 8)
  - Data tapes related to the epidemiological study (9), undated (Box 315, Item 1)
  - Reels of film labeled Bolivia Part I, II, III, and IV (7 reels), undated (Box 315, Item 2)
  - Audiotapes labeled "Bolivia, RISM U.S. Productions" (3), undated (Box 315, Item 3)
  - DAT tape labeled "Bolivia, RISM U.S. Productions", undated (Box 315, Item 4)
  - Scripts related to RISM U.S. Productions films Lake Titicaca, A Land Conquered, and The Revolution, undated (Box 315, Item 5)
  - Epidemiological Studies in Bolivia: Final Epidemiological Report for the Peace Corps, 1967 (Box 315, Item 6)
  - Estudios Epidemiologicos en Bolivia: Reporte Epidemiologico Final para el Cuerpo de Paz, 1967 (Box 315, Item 7)
- Appendix: Exhibition Material
  - Promotional brochures, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - Promotional brochures, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 2)
  - Promotional brochures, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - Promotional brochures, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - Bolivia Studyman labels, undated (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - Bolivia Project videotape, undated (Box 317, Item 1)
  - Exhibition poster: RISM Bolivia Project, 1964-1967, undated (Box 318, Item 1)
  - Exhibition poster: Bolivia: RISM Bolivia Project Study Communities, undated (Box 318, Item 2)
- Appendix: Computer Cards
  - Name Card: Coroico, undated (Box 319)
  - Name Card: Coroico, Villa Abecia, Reyes, San Miguel, undated (Box 320)
  - Name Card: San Miguel, undated (Box 321)
  - Name Card: Reyes, undated (Box 322)
  - Name Card: Reyes, undated (Box 323)
  - Name Card: Compi, undated (Box 324)
  - Name Card: Unlabeled, undated (Box 325)
  - Name Card: Sorata, San Miguel, undated (Box 326)
  - Unlabeled tab cards, undated (Box 327)
  - Maney 3/5, undated (Box 328)
  - Census Data Cards: Coroico, 1966 (Box 329)
  - Census Data Cards: Coroico, Mururata, Cruz Loma, Sorata, 1966 (Box 330)
  - Census Data Cards: Sorata, Reyes, 1966 (Box 331)
  - Census Data Cards: San Miguel, Llamachchi, 1966 (Box 332)
  - Census Data Cards: Compi, Villa Abecia, 1966 (Box 333)
  - Data Coded Binder: Political Activity, undated (Box 334)
  - Data Coded Binder: Stratification, undated (Box 335)
  - Data Coded Binder: Community Action, undated (Box 336)
  - Data Coded Binder: Group Structure, undated (Box 337)
- Appendix: Publication Materials
  - Documentation regarding Klein and Kelley's Revolution and the Birth of Inequality (1981), undated (Box 338)
  - Ethnographic Report, undated (Box 40)
    **JM: I have been unable to locate this subseries.
    - Comm. Outlines, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Sorata--Chapter Prep, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Villa Abecia--Chapter Draft, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Reyes--Chapter Prep, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Coroico--Chapter Prep, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Villa Abecia--Blanca Muratorio, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Sorata--Isabella Conti, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Community Setting: Reyes--Marta Callejo, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Introduction--Adrienne Aron, Coroico, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Part II: Villa Abecia, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Chapter Two: Power & Authority, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Tape three, side one Villa Abecia con't., undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Chapter Four: Groups & Organizations, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Chapter Five: Community Action, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Building a Road to the River, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Chapter Five: Community Action, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Part II: Community Social Structure. B: Social Strat., undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Power & Authority, undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Appendix: Photocopied Materials
  - Carbon Copies of Field Notes: Coroico, undated (Box 339)
  - Carbon Copies of Field Notes: Coroico, San Miguel, Compi, undated (Box 340)
  - Carbon Copies of Field Notes: Villa Abecia (5 vol.), undated (Box 341)
  - Carbon Copies of Field Notes: Sorata, undated (Box 342)
  - Carbon Copies of Field Notes: Reyes, Sorata, undated (Box 343)
  - Villa Abecia: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 1)
  - Villa Abecia: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 2)
  - Villa Abecia: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 3)
  - Compi 1: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 4)
  - Compi (101-129): Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 5)
  - Compi (130-156): Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 6)
  - Compi (1-49): Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - Compi School: Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 8)
  - San Miguel: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 9)
  - San Miguel: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 10)
  - San Miguel: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 11)
  - Reyes (Household Sanitation): Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Reyes: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - Reyes: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - Reyes (Household Sanitation): Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 4)
  - Reyes: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Reyes: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Reyes: Household Administrative Cards and Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 7)
  - Reyes Schools: Records of Laboratory Results, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 8)
  - La Paz (Maternidad Hospital): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 9)
  - La Paz (Caja Nacional): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 10)
  - La Paz (Thorax Institute): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 11)
  - La Paz (Centro de Salud Publica): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 12)
  - Penas (Esquillan): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 13)
  - Penas (Catacora): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 14)
  - Penas (Catecus GP): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 15)
  - Penas (Pajcha): Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 16)
  - Penas: Records of Laboratory Results, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 17)
  - Unlabeled carbon copies, undated (Box 345, Folder 18)
  - Carbon Copies of Records of Laboratory Results (7 packets), undated (Box 346)
- Appendix: Reports from RISM to the Peace Corps, Partial Reports Related to the RISM Bolivia Project, 1964-1967
  - Public Health Research in Bolivia, 1964 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - A Study of Child Development in the Bolivian Altiplano, undated (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Agrarian Reform & Migration on the Bolivian Altiplano, 1966 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Distribution List: A.A.A. Bolivia Papers, undated (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Excerpt from untitled manuscript: "Section 1: The Community, The Geography." (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Community Health Studies, undated (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Comitas: Education and Social Stratification in Contemporary Bolivia, undated (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Huatajata, General Observations (excerpt from manuscript), undated (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - Health, undated (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - Madeline, Barbara Leons: Land Reform in the Bolivian Yungas., undated (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - McEwan, undated (Box 272, Folder 11)
  - Muratorio, undated (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Muratorio, Social, and Participation of the non-Yungan Campesinos: English and Spanish, undated (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - Aron, undated (Box 272, Folder 14)
  - Victor Novick: Too Many Indians, Not Enough Chiefs: Leadership Crisis in a Bolivian Hacienda Town., undated (Box 272, Folder 15)
  - Novick, undated (Box 272, Folder 16)
  - Background and Proposal for Field Work, Summer 1965, by Susan Sorinshaw (Box 272, Folder 17)
  - Maru Sera Sample: Total Epidemiological Sample., undated (Box 272, Folder 18)
  - Orio Figures and References, undated (Box 272, Folder 19)
  - Zaki Copy: Acknowledgements, References, Epidemiological., undated (Box 272, Folder 20)
  - Technological Report on the Epidemiological Study, 1965 (Box 272, Folder 21)
  - Quarterly Report #8, September 1966 (Box 272, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Report #4, October 1965 (Box 272, Folder 23)